here are the stories we're covering this
여기 우리가 다루고 있는 이야기들이 있습니다.
week in the category 5 TV newsroom
카테고리 5 주 TV 뉴스 룸
Germany's Supreme Court has rejected a
독일의 대법원이 거부 한
legal case that sought to stop people
사람들을 막으려 고 한 법적 사건
using the popular adblock plus program
인기있는 애드 블록 플러스 프로그램 사용
that removes ads from websites a Chinese
즉, 중국의 웹 사이트에서 광고를 제거
web giant has found a Windows zero day
웹 거인이 윈도우 제로 데이를 발견 했다.
and is keeping the details quiet while
세부 사항을 조용하게 유지하면서
working with Microsoft on the issue an
Microsoft와 협력하여
unpatched vulnerabilities been found in
패치되지 않은 취약점 이에서 발견되었습니다.
the Nintendo switch that can be
될 수있는 Nintendo 스위치
exploited to run custom code and do you
사용자 정의 코드를 실행하기 위해 악용되고
run Drupal you need to upgrade
당신이 업그레이 드해야 Drupal 을 실행
immediately these stories are coming
즉시이 이야기들이오고있다.
right up don't go anywhere
바로 어디 가지 마세요
Jeff Weston GEMA you're building a
제프 웨스턴 GEMA
brand-new beautiful website what aren't
전혀 새로운 아름다운 웹 사이트
you you're terrible actor what this
너 너 끔찍한 배우 야 너 뭐야?
where acting comes into play you're
연기가 시작되면
supposed to act okay are you building a
행동하라 .
really cool website are you building a
정말 멋진 웹 사이트 는
really cool website just because Jeff is
Jeff가 있기 때문에 정말 멋진 웹 사이트입니다.
confused doesn't mean you have to be
혼란 스러울 지라도 당신이해야한다는 것은 아닙니다 .
visit cap five dot TV slash DreamHost to
방문 모자 다섯 도트 TV 슬래시 DreamHost 에
sign up for unlimited web hosting for
무제한 웹 호스팅 에 가입
your website with unlimited email
무제한 이메일을 사용하는 웹 사이트
accounts MySQL databases
계정 MySQL 데이터베이스
the latest version of PHP WordPress and
PHP는 워드 프레스의 최신 버전과
more and even a free domain name
더 많은 무료 도메인 이름
registration it's less than six dollars
등록은 6 달러 미만입니다.
per month so sign up today cat five dot
한 달에 5 개가 넘는 고양이를 등록하십시오.
TV slash dream host this is the category
TV 슬래시 꿈 주 이것은 카테고리입니다
5 TV news room covering the week's top
5 주간의 TV 뉴스 룸
tech stories with a slight linux bytes
약간의 리눅스 바이트를 가진 하이테크 이야기
I'm Sasha Rickman and here the top
나는 Sasha Rickman이고 여기는 톱이다.
stories were following this week
이야기가 이번 주 다음에 있었다.
Germany's Supreme Court has rejected a
독일의 대법원이 거부 한
legal case that sought to stop people
사람들을 막으려 고 한 법적 사건
using the popular adblock plus program
인기있는 애드 블록 플러스 프로그램 사용
that removes ads from web sites the
웹 사이트 에서 광고를 제거 하는
lawsuit was started three years ago by
3 년 전에 소송이 시작 되었습니다.
German publishing a German publishing
독일어 출판 독일 출판
giant Axel Springer it alleged that the
거대한 악셀 스프링거 (Axel Springer) 는
way adblock the bad block plus stopped
방법 adblock 나쁜 블록 더하기 중지
people seeing advertisements on its
광고 를 본 사람들
sites amounted to unfair competition
불공정 경쟁 사이트
Axel Springer said that it would
Axel Springer는
continue its legal challenge by taking
법적인 도전을 계속 한다.
the issue to Germany's Constitutional
독일의 헌법 문제
Court the German publishing firm first
독일 출판사를 먼저 재판하라.
complained about adblock plus in 2015
2015 년에 adblock plus에 대해 불평했다.
alleging that it broke competition laws
경쟁법을 위반 했다고 주장
by letting firms pay to be on a
수 있도록함으로써 기업은에있을 지불
whitelist to stop their ads being
광고 게재를 중단하는 허용 목록
blocked it took the case to the Supreme
그것은 대법원에 사건 을 가져 갔다.
Court after losing the first round of
첫 라운드를 패한 후 법원
legal action in 2015 other German media
2015 년 기타 법적 조치
firms that also launched related legal
관련 법률을 시작한 기업
actions said the simple blocking of ads
행동은 광고의 단순한 차단이라고
was a violation of local laws designed
지역 법의 위반이 설계되었습니다
to promote competition the Supreme Court
경쟁을 촉진하기 위해 대법원
disagreed with Springer's allegations
스프링거의 주장에 동의하지 않는다.
and said no laws were being broken
아무런 법률도 깨지지 않았다고 말했다.
because it was up to individual users
개별 사용자에게 달려 있기 때문에
whether or not they used the software
그들이 소프트웨어 를 사용했는지 여부
the creators of adblock plus welcomed
Adblock 작성자들 환영
the ruling and said in a statement that
판결을 내리고 성명서 에서
it was excited that Germany's highest
독일 최고의
court upheld the right every internet
법원은 모든 인터넷 권리를지지했습니다.
citizen possesses to block unwanted
시민들은 원치 않는 것을
advertising online after the verdict
평결 후 온라인 광고
class Hendrik sewing Springer's a head
학급 Hendrik 바느질 스프링 거는 머리
of media law said the ruling was an
언론법에 따르면 판결은
attack on the heart of the free media so
무료 미디어의 마음 등등 공격
is it an attack on the heart of free
그것은 자유의 마음에 대한 공격인가?
media no I don't think so at all I don't
미디어 아니, 전혀 그렇게 생각 하지 않아.
think so nope not at all I I think this
그렇게 생각하지 마라. 나는 이것을 생각한다.
is a great ruling and I think it was a
위대한 판결이며 나는 그것이
proper ruling now granted it's probably
적절한 판결이 이제는 아마 주어질 것입니다.
based on German law so depending on what
독일 법률에 따라 그렇게
each country has for their own laws
각국은 자국의 법률을 가지고있다.
would dictate how the court would be
법원이 어떻게 될 것인지 명령 할 것이다.
able to make a determination but I
결심을 할 수는 있지만 나
completely 100% stand behind Germany's
독일에 100 % 완전히 뒤지고있다.
Supreme Court on this because if you
대법원은 이것에 대해
if you say legally in court you are not
법정에서 법적으로 말하면
allowed to deny advertisements you have
가지고있는 광고 를 거부 할 수 있음
just commercialized the human race and
단지 인류를 상업화했다.
quite frankly that's a right that is
솔직히 말해서 그것이 바로
individual so I stand with the the
개인적으로 나는
German Court on this one if I don't want
이것에 대한 독일 법원 , 내가 원하지 않는다면
to see ads I don't want to see it I
광고를보고 나는 그것을 내가보고 싶지 않아
think that this is a very polarizing
이것은 매우 편광이라고 생각
topic in that if you're in the free
주제는 당신이 자유 에 있다면
media that you have to be able to
당신이 할 수 있어야하는 미디어
generate revenue so here's the thing my
여기에 일이 그래서 수익을 창출 내
newsstand as a newspaper used to be a
신문으로 신문 가판대가
physical newsstand I used to have paper
내가 가지고 있던 신문 가판대
boys on the corners selling newspapers
신문 판매 코너
for a nickel
니켈
and that was my revenue stream and
그것은 내 수입 흐름이었고
people would buy the newspaper from the
사람들은에서 신문을 살 것
local store now my revenue stream if you
지역 상점에 지금 내 수입원
will becomes a website and it's very
웹 사이트가 될 것이고 그것은 매우
competitive it's highly competitive
경쟁 이 치열하다.
because everything that's on the
에있는 모든 것이
Internet is expected to be free so if I
인터넷이 무료라면
now put advertising on my site in order
내 사이트 에 순서대로 광고 게재
to be the compensation for the
보상에 대한 보상
distribution of my news and then you
내 뉴스를 배포 한 다음에
block it there's the other perspective
다른 관점을 차단하십시오.
Jeff no and I get that perspective but
Jeff no와 나는 그 원근법을 얻는다.
here's my take on it advertising on the
여기 광고에 내 걸릴
Internet is not like traditional
인터넷은 전통 과 같지 않습니다.
advertising if you turn on the TV you
당신 이 TV를 켜면 광고
get commercials you get a specific
특정 광고를 얻으십시오.
commercial that's been purchased to air
상업용으로 구매 한 상업용
at a certain time regardless of what
무엇을 막론 하고 어떤 시간에
your personal life circumstances are you
너의 개인적인 삶의 환경은 너야.
go to online advertising and it's based
온라인 광고에 가서 그것을 기반으로
on the cookies and the data and the
쿠키와 데이터 및
information that's shared through your
귀하가 공유 한 정보
internet usage so it's not generic
일반 인터넷 사용법이 아닌 인터넷 사용법
advertising it's specific targeted
그것은 특정의 광고 대상
advertising and that is what I think
광고 하고 그것이 내가 생각하는 것입니다.
acceptable to be blocked if somebody
누군가가
says look I don't want my personal data
나는 내 개인 데이터를 원하지 않는다고 말한다.
being used to advertise back to me thank
내가 감사에 다시 광고하는 데 사용되는
you leave me alone so if that was the
당신 이 저를 내버려두면
case then could we not say let's make it
그렇다면 우리는 그것을 만들자고 말할 수 없다.
so the adblock plus for example in the
예를 들어 adblock 에
in the case of this story was to give an
이 이야기 의 경우 에는
opt-out command to the advertising that
광고 게재를 선택 해제 합니다.
says no tracking no tracking code
추적 코드를 추적 하지 않음
and only display generic ads and the
일반 광고 만 표시 하고
only thing that they're allowed to
그들이 허용하는 경우에만 일
display are those generic ads that
디스플레이는
traditional media would have been
전통적인 미디어는했을 것이다
purchasing would have been selling I'd
구매했을 땐 내가 팔았을거야.
be okay with that
그게 좋을거야.
I really would because then it's not
다음은 아니기 때문에 정말 것
targeted advertising based on your
귀하의
individual online profile its generic
개별 온라인 프로필 일반
advertising a Chinese web giant has
중국 웹 거인있다 광고
found a Windows zero day and is keeping
윈도 제로 데이를 발견하고 지키고있다.
the details quiet while working with
함께 일하는 동안 조용한 세부 사항
Microsoft on the issue Chinese company
Microsoft 는 문제에 중국 회사
cui ho 360 says it is found a zero a
cui ho 360은 그것이 0이라는 것을 발견했다고 말합니다.
Windows zero day in the wild but because
야생의 Windows 제로 데이지 만 때문에
it has notified Microsoft it is not
Microsoft에 통지 하지 않았습니다.
telling anyone else how it works the
그것이 작동하는 방법을 다른 사람에게 이야기
company announced an apt attack on the
회사는
unspecified zero day of the unspecified
불특정 다수의 제로 데이
zero day on a global scale it called the
세계적인 규모의 제로 데이 .
vulnerability a double-kill bug said it
취약점은 더블 킬 버그가 그것을 말했다
exploits the latest version of Internet
최신 인터넷 버전을 악용하다 .
Explorer and applications that use the
Explorer 를 사용 하는 탐색기 및 응용 프로그램
IE kernel and added that it's being
IE 커널 과 그것이되고 있다고 덧붙였다.
spread in Microsoft Office documents
Microsoft Office 문서에 확산
that include a malicious web page if a
이 경우 악성 웹 페이지 가 포함됩니다.
victim opens the document the post
희생자 가 문서를 열면 게시물
claims the malicious code will run in
악의적 인 코드가 실행될 것이라고 주장
the background to execute the
실행하기위한 배경
unspecified attack program it's only
불특정 공격 프로그램
illustration of the attack is in the
공격의 그림은에
Chinese language annotated image Chinese
중국어 언어 주석 이미지 Chinese
language annotated image shown here
여기에 표시된 언어 주석 이미지
Microsoft would far prefer that users
Microsoft는 사용자를 훨씬 선호합니다.
stopped using Internet Explorer and
Internet Explorer 및
adopt its edge browser instead some
가장자리 브라우저 대신 일부 채택
users are proven approving stubborn
사용자가 완고함을 인정 하는 것으로 입증되었습니다.
however according to net market share ie
그러나 순 시장 점유율 즉
still has a arrested arrested on twelve
아직 12 명 으로 체포 됐어 .
percent of the browser market that is
브라우저 시장의 퍼센트
why it's why last week patch last week's
지난주에 왜 지난 주에 패치 가 나왔는지
Patch Tuesday plugged a serious if
패치 화요일 에 심각한 문제가 발생했습니다.
legacy IE vulnerability CVE 2014 - zero
레거시 IE 취약점 CVE 2014 - zero
322 a remote code execution bug I don't
322 내가하지 않는 원격 코드 실행 버그
use edge I don't I don't like edge I
내가 가장자리를 싫어하지 않는 가장자리를 사용하여 I
think people are going to use edge so
사람들이 너무 가장자리를 사용하려고 생각
what's the next best I don't know where
내가 어디 있는지 모르는 차선책 은 무엇인가?
I'll be can you weigh in on this what's
나는 너에게 이것에 무게를 달 수있을거야.
the next best browser to use if
다음 에 사용할 최상의 브라우저
oK we've got internet explorer as the
우리는 인터넷 익스플로러를
first option edge is the second and her
첫번째 선택권 가장자리 는 두번째이고 그녀
question is what's the next what is what
질문은 다음 무엇입니까?
is the browser that is apt to be
알맞은 브라우저입니다 .
exploitable ensure and maybe conforms to
악용 가능 하고 준수 할 수 있음
standards and is innovative is fast is
표준 은 빠르고 혁신적인 제품 입니다.
good on resources those kinds of things
그 종류의 것들에 좋은 자원
so obviously you know we're gonna look
그래서 분명히 우리가봤을거야.
at the top two which are firefox and
상단이되는 파이어 폭스와 있습니다
chrome plain is simple now you can get
크롬 일반은 간단하다 지금은 얻을 수 있습니다
into other ones opera and if you want to
다른 오페라로, 그리고 원한다면
try out some of the obscure ones that's
의 모호한 것들 중 일부를 시도
fine too but realistically Chrome
너무 좋지만 사실적으로 Chrome
Firefox they're about on par believe it
파이어 폭스 가 믿고있는 파이어 폭스
or not now especially with Firefox 57
지금은 특히 Firefox 57과는 다릅니다.
which uses less memory than earlier
이는 이전보다 적은 메모리를 사용
versions of Firefox is faster and even
파이어 폭스의 버전 이 빠르다.
boasts that it's faster than chrome I
Chrome 보다 빠르다고 자랑 합니다.
don't know if that's true yet I haven't
그게 사실인지 아직 모르겠다.
benchmarked it myself I've had problems
벤치마킹 을 통해 문제 가 발생했습니다.
with Firefox in the past with memory
파이어 폭스 와 함께 메모리 가 있는 과거
leaks and I don't like Firefox's
누수 와 나는 파이어 폭스를 좋아하지 않는다.
approach to the app ecosystem the attack
앱 생태계에 대한 접근 방식
the add-on ecosystem in that I think
내가 생각하기에 애드온 생태계
that any browser that kills off their
그것들 을 죽이는 모든 브라우저
entire developer base like they did is
전체 개발자 기반 은
with with Firefox 56 I think is that's
파이어 폭스 56과 함께 나는 그것이
that's just a no-no to me I think that
그 날에 단지 더 노 없습니다 나는 생각
they really needed to work with their
그들은 정말로 그들 과 함께 일할 필요 가있었습니다.
developers better so that was a bit of a
개발자가 더 좋았 습니다.
red flag now
지금 붉은 깃발
both browsers are excellent Chrome
두 브라우저 모두 우수한 크롬입니다.
Firefox Sasha can you can you imagine
Firefox Sasha 당신은 상상할 수 있습니까?
you know my first question to you is
당신은 내 첫 질문 을 안다.
gonna be do you have a Firefox phone or
될거야 당신은 파이어 폭스 폰이 있거나 않습니다
do you have an Android phone I have an
너는 가지고있는 안드로이드 전화 가 있니?
Android phone you have an Android phone
Android 휴대 전화를 가지고있는 Android 휴대 전화
so we have to just think about the fact
그래서 우리는 사실에 대해서 생각 해야만합니다.
that okay what one is going to work
그게 뭘 하려는지 알았어.
better for you Chrome or Firefox so if
크롬이나 파이어 폭스가 더 좋다면 if
they're pretty much matched up as far as
그들은 꽤 많이 일치 한다.
the quality the browser goes at this
브라우저가 이걸로 가는 품질
point which one is going to work better
하나 가 더 잘 작동 할 지점
for you now chrome is developed by
이제 크롬은에 의해 개발되었습니다.
Google the same company that
Google과 같은 회사
manufactures your phone's operating
휴대 전화를 제조하다
system Android so part of chrome is that
시스템 안드로이드는 너무 크롬의 일부이다
you can login to your Google profile and
Google 프로필에 로그인 하고
it gives you access to things like
그것은 당신에게 같은 것들에 대한 액세스를 제공합니다.
shared bookmarks with your phone shared
공유 된 북마크 공유
bookmarks with your other computers
다른 컴퓨터와 북마크하기
using Chrome and it gives you shared
Chrome을 사용하면 공유 기능을 제공합니다.
access to your history
당신의 역사에 대한 접근
and passwords and things that you do
암호 및 할 일
within that Google ecosystem so as an
Google 생태계 내 에서
Android user would you find benefit to
Android 사용자는 다음과 같은 이점을 누릴 수 있습니다.
the fact that you're accessing your
귀하가 귀하의
email in the same way on multiple
여러 번에 같은 방식으로 이메일 보내기
different platforms and you're nodding
다른 플랫폼 과 당신은 끄덕이다.
and I think that the answer is probably
그 대답은 아마도
yeah in your case would then be Chrome
그렇다면 귀하의 경우 크롬 것입니다
is probably the best browser for you
아마 당신을위한 최고의 브라우저입니다
Firefox doesn't offer that same kind of
파이어 폭스의 동일한 종류를 제공하지 않습니다
functionality that is going to be tied
묶일 기능
into your phone the way that the Google
휴대 전화 방식이에 구글
browser is so that's where I would
브라우저는 내가 원하는 곳이다.
probably lean in your case and using
아마 당신의 경우에 의지 하고 사용하기.
Chrome is safe against an attack like
Chrome은 다음과 같은 공격에 대해 안전합니다.
this we have to work we have to be wise
우리가해야 할 일은 우리 가 현명해야한다는 것입니다.
we have to always be mindful that
우리는 항상 염두해야
fisher's which are folks that are out
밖으로 피셔하는 있습니다 사람들
there trying to get your information
거기에 귀하의 정보를 얻으 려고
they're out there tricking users they're
그들은 거기서 사용자를 속이며
bringing up browser windows so web pages
웹 페이지가되도록 브라우저 창 가져 오기
essentially that look like error
본질적으로 오류처럼 보입니다.
messages that look like a Windows error
윈도우 오류처럼 메시지
and click here to to fix it or call this
여기 를 클릭 하여 수정하거나 전화하세요.
number to reach out to Microsoft because
번호 는 Microsoft에 연락하기 때문에
we've got a patch for your computer
우리는 당신의 컴퓨터를위한 패치를 가지고있다.
these kinds of things so as long as
그래서만큼 사물의 이러한 종류의
you're privy to the fact that hey there
너 거기 헤이 사실에 대해서 너는 간통하다.
are web threats out there that you need
필요한 웹 위협 이 있습니다.
to watch out for on any browser you need
모든 브라우저에 당신이 필요로 조심하는
to be smart about those things and and
그런 것들과 약 현명하게
part of that is just knowing that you
그 중 일부는 단지 당신이
need to watch out for those things then
다음 것들을 조심해야
yeah you're safer now what it boils down
네가 지금 안전 해 졌어.
to here with IE is that the things that
여기 IE와는
are happening do not require the user to
사용자를 필요로하지 않는 일이있다
do an idiotic thing that's what it boils
그것이 바보짓을 하는 바보 같은 짓을해라.
down to so with the old Outlook Express
기존 Outlook Express 와 함께
if you simply touched an email that had
당신이 단순히 이메일을 만졌을 때
malware on it boom you're infected you
그것에 악성 코드가 붐 을 일으켰습니다.
didn't even have to open it you didn't
심지어 당신은하지 않았다 열 필요가 없었어요
even have to click a link it was in your
심지어 당신의 링크를 클릭해야합니다.
system what is it with Microsoft
시스템 Microsoft와의 관계
products that was a Microsoft product
Microsoft 제품이었다 제품
now Internet Explorer same thing you
지금 Internet Explorer 똑같은 당신
simply touch that link and boom you're
간단히 그 링크를 터치하고 붐을 일으키는 것입니다.
infected you've got this malware
이 멀웨어에 감염되었습니다.
whatever the zero day is that's the
제로 데이가 뭐든간에
exploit and it can get into your system
악용하고 시스템에 침투 할 수 있다.
if you're not patched and they're you
네가 패치되지 않았고 그들이 너라면.
know they're Microsoft's looking at it
그들이 마이크로 소프트가 그것을보고 있다는 것을 알고 있다.
and saying oh that's an old browser we
오, 그건 오래된 브라우저 라구.
don't support it we don't want people
그것을 지지하지 않는다. 우리는 사람들을 원하지 않는다.
using it do we even want to patch it
그것을 사용하여 우리는 그것을 패치하고 싶습니다.
I guess we'd better but they're not you
우리가 더 나아질 거라고 생각하지만 너는 아니야.
know that's not the game that they're
그게 그들이하는 게임이 아니라는 걸 알아.
wanted to play so yes chrome is going to
그래, 크롬 연주 하려고 했어 .
be safer because those exploits are not
그 악용은 그렇지 않기 때문에 더 안전해야합니다.
a part of chrome and the development
크롬의 일부 와 개발
ecosystem of Chrome and Firefox indeed
참 으로 크롬과 파이어 폭스의 생태계
is based on a completely different model
전혀 다른 모델을 기반으로합니다.
to that of Microsoft now one thing that
마이크로 소프트 이제 한 가지의 해당
does give me pause for concern about
내게 잠시 걱정을 안겨 준다 .
this story is in my experience in
이 이야기는 내 경험에있다.
dealing with government resources I
정부 자원 다루기 I
would say that generally governments lag
일반적으로 정부가 지체 한다고 말한다.
behind on updating and as of a year ago
업데이트 중이고 1 년 전
I know when I was looking at some
내가 어떤 것을 보고 있었을 때 나는 알고 있다.
government infrastructure for a client
클라이언트를위한 정부 인프라
of mine they were using Internet
내 그들은 인터넷을 사용했다
Explorer because they still had Windows
그들이 Windows 를 여전히 가지고 있기 때문에 탐색기
and T right and I'm going wow I can't
그리고 T right 그리고 나는 와우가 될 수 없어.
believe this is on a government computer
정부 컴퓨터 에 있다고 생각해.
so if you've got government computers
정부 컴퓨터가 있다면
that potentially are still using a
잠재적 으로 여전히
software like operating systems that are
의 운영 체제와 같은 소프트웨어
just full of holes but you're still
구멍이 가득 차 있지만 아직도
using Internet Explorer and you haven't
Internet Explorer를 사용 하면
updated massive massive problems so it
대대적 인 대규모 문제를 업데이트 했습니다.
would be better if just we switch to
우리가로 전환하면 더 좋을거야.
Linux yes well played don't say that
잘한다는 말을하지 않습니다 재생 예 리눅스
with the Frey at the end it's not it's
마지막에 프레이와 그렇지 그것의의
not a question it's a statement if you
없는 질문은 당신의 경우 성명의
wanted to go there and I think you know
거기에 가고 싶었어. 네가 아는 것 같아.
you hit the nail on the head there Jeff
제프 의 머리에 못 을 박 았어.
where you know the government has
정부가 알고있는 곳
trouble keeping up with the technology
기술에 뒤지지 않는 문제
because they don't have the manpower
인력이 없기 때문에
they don't have the resources to
그들에게는 자원이 없다.
constantly be upgrading and improving
끊임없이 업그레이드하고 개선하고있다.
things and quite frankly and a lot of
사물 과 솔직히 말해서
government IT departments are folks that
정부 IT 부서는
went to school back in the 90s and are
90 년대에 학교에 다시 가서 있습니다
trained based on 90s tech and if you're
90 년대 기술 에 기반한 교육을 받았고
running NT on your server well that's
서버에서 NT를 실행 하면됩니다.
probably because you were educated in
아마 당신이 교육을하고 있기 때문에
the 90s and haven't improved upon that
90 년대와 그것에 개선되지 않았습니다
education but but also there's the fact
교육 그러나 또한 사실 거기
that some people some companies are held
어떤 사람들은 몇몇 회사 들이
back by
뒤로
the technologies that they've invested
그들이 투자 한 기술
in so you think about an activex
그래서 당신은 액티브 엑스 에 대해 생각해 봅니다.
development where they've paid tens of
그들이 수십억 달러를 지불 한 개발
thousands of dollars to build on the
온 건설하는 수천 달러
internet explorer' architecture a piece
인터넷 탐색기의 아키텍처
of software that is for their internal
내부 용 소프트웨어
intranet for example so now you tell
인트라넷 예 를 들어 그래서 지금 말해
them they need to move to chrome and
크롬 으로 이동 해야 합니다.
they look at that twenty thousand dollar
그들은 그 2 만 달러를 본다.
bill that they paid ten years ago and
이 법안들은 10 년 전 지불 있고
say oh you know what we're not going to
오, 우리가 가려고 하지 않을 것을 알고있다.
do it right we're not going to rebuild
우리가 재건 하지 않을거야.
our entire intranet an unmatchable
우리의 전체 인트라넷을 unmatchable
vulnerability has been found in the
취약성이
Nintendo switch that can be exploited to
악용 될 수있는 Nintendo 스위치
run custom code security researcher Kay
사용자 지정 코드 보안 연구원 Kay 실행
Temkin has released proof of concept
Temkin은 개념 증명을 발표했습니다.
code dubbed fuse a chalet that exploits
익스플로잇 하는 샬레 라고 불리는 코드
a bug in Nvidia's Tegra chipsets to run
Nvidia의 Tegra 칩셋에서 발생하는 버그
custom code on locked down devices
잠긴 장치의 사용자 정의 코드
Temkin who participates in the Nintendo
Nintendo에 참여하는 Temkin
switch hacking project Ries which has
이있는 프로젝트 RIES는 해킹 전환
developed a cold boot hack for the games
게임용 콜드 부트 해킹 개발
console that takes advantage of an
의 장점을 취하는 콘솔
uncatchable blender in the Tegra boot
테그라 부츠 에서 uncatchable 믹서기
ROM she's also working on a customized
ROM 그녀는 또한 맞춤형 작업을하고 있습니다.
switch firmware called atmosphere which
분위기라고하는 스위치 펌웨어
can be installed via fuse a gele
퓨즈를 통해 젤을 설치할 수있다.
essentially if you say jelly exploits a
본질적으로 젤리가
vulnerability during a switches startup
스위치를 시작할 때의 취약점
to commandeer the gadget and executes
가제트를 징집 하고 실행
unofficial software this is useful for
비공식적 인 소프트웨어 로
unlocking the locked down Nintendo
잠겨있는 닌텐도를 잠금 해제
switch so that homebrew games custom
홈브류 게임 맞춤형으로 전환
firmware and other code can be run
펌웨어 및 기타 코드를 실행할 수 있습니다.
you'll need physical access to the
당신은에 물리적으로 접근해야합니다
hardware during powerup to perform fuse
퓨즈를 수행 하는 전원 공급 중 하드웨어
a gele it's not something that can be
쥬레는 그것을 할 수있는 일이 아니다
pulled off over-the-air in a blog post
블로그 포스트에서 공중파 를 날려 버렸다.
outlining her findings earlier this
이전에 그녀의 연구 결과를 요약
month
달
Temkin explained the relevant
Temkin은 관련
vulnerability is the result of a coding
취약점은 코딩 의 결과이다.
mistake in the read-only boot ROM found
읽기 전용 부팅 ROM에서 실수가 발견되었습니다.
in most Tegra devices Temkin reckoned
Temkin은 대부분의 Tegra 장치에서
the issue is present in all Nintendo
문제는 모든 닌텐도에 존재한다.
switches the nature of the flaw is such
결함 의 본질을 바꾸어 놓는다.
that it will require a hardware revision
하드웨어 수정 이 필요할 것 입니다.
to fix the boot rom which contains the
를 포함하는 부트 롬 을 고치기 위해
programming bug accepts minor patches in
프로그래밍 버그가
the factory but cannot be updated
공장은 업데이트 할 수 없다 .
afterwards according to Tompkins
이후 Tompkins 에 따르면
that means once a vulnerable machine
그것은 일단 취약한 기계를 의미합니다.
rolls off the assembly line the
조립 라인을 굴러서
vulnerability is baked in and cannot be
취약점 은 구워지고있을 수 없다.
mitigated Temkin says that the exploit
완화 된 Temkin은 악용이
was responsibly disclosed to and
책임감 있게
forwarded to other vendors that use
사용 하는 다른 공급 업체로 전달
Tegra embedded processors including
Tegra 임베디드 프로세서
Nintendo successful exploitation
Nintendo 성공적인 착취
compromises the processors root of trust
프로세서 루트의 신뢰를 손상시킨다.
and provides the attacker with access to
공격자 에게
secrets burned into device fuses as well
장치 퓨즈에 구운 비밀
as following arbitrary code execution
다음과 같은 임의 코드 실행
while such an exploit could be used for
반면 이러한 사용될 수 있습니다 악용
malware that compromises the users
사용자 를 해치는 멀웨어
personal data due to the very nature of
개인 데이터 는 본질적으로
the Nintendo switch being a gaming
Nintendo 스위치 는 게임 이되고있다 .
console it's most likely that this will
그것은이 의지가 대부분의 콘솔
be exploited to route the device and
기기 를 라우팅하기 위해 악용 되고
create custom boot loaders for side
사이드 용 사용자 정의 부트 로더 작성
loading unofficial applications full
비공식 응용 프로그램 전체 로드
details of the bug is set to be revealed
버그의 세부 사항 이 밝혀 지도록 설정되어있다.
on June 15th 2018 unless it is made
그것이 만들어 지지 않는 한 2018 년 6 월 15 일에
public by others first a parallel effort
다른 사람들에 의해 먼저 공개적 으로 노력
to create custom firmware for the switch
스위치에 대한 사용자 지정 펌웨어 를 만드는 방법
using the vulnerability or one
취약점 또는 하나를 사용하여
substantially similar is underway by a
실질적으로 유사하다 .
group called team executors so I love my
그룹이라고 팀 집행 그래서 사랑 내
switch I have one I love it I use it
스위치 하나는 내가 그것을 사랑 내가 가지고 그것을 사용
often but that's besides the point
종종 그것은 요점 외에도
I use my switch and I wonder if it could
내 스위치를 사용하고있을 수 있는지 궁금해.
be dual booted like if I could have my
내가 가지고있을 수있는 것처럼 이중 부팅해라.
switch and then also have this alternate
스위치를 누른 다음이 대체
thing where I could turn it into
일 전으로 바꿀 수있는 곳
something more we'll see I suppose at
우리가 볼 수 있는 것보다 더 많이 나는
the end of the day it's possible I mean
하루의 끝은 무슨 뜻 가능
that's where the exploit is is in the
(가) 악용 곳은에서입니다입니다
boot sequence so if you do have a way to
부팅 순서를 바꿀 수 있습니다.
physically get to it and and you know
육체적으로 그것에 도착하면
input this code that gives you a dual
입력 당신에게 듀얼을 제공합니다 코드
startup I mean it's it's entirely
시작 그건 내가 완전히 의미하는거야.
possible absolutely but the one thing I
가능 하지만 절대적으로 나는
was wondering though is because it's I
그것이 내가이기 때문에 그래도 궁금해했다.
mean because it's a physical you have to
네가해야할 육체적 인 의미이기 때문에
physically be there to get the the code
물리적으로 코드 를 가져올 수 있어야합니다.
in is this really going to be such an
이게 진짜로 그렇게 될거야 .
issue with a concern for malware I mean
악성 코드에 대한 우려가 있음을 의미합니다.
how many people are gonna break into
얼마나 많은 사람들이 침입 할 것인가 ?
home hookup to a switch put the code in
스위치에 홈 훅업 코드 삽입
now access your data on the network
이제 네트워크에서 데이터에 액세스 하십시오.
I have to ask though Sasha how how do
나는 사샤에게 어떻게해야하는지 물어봐야 만한다.
you get games on the switch how do they
당신은 스위치에서 게임을 얻습니다. 어떻게해야합니까?
end up on the switch I have to buy them
내가 그걸 사야하는 스위치에서 끝내라.
yeah do you remember the Nintendo DSi
네 , 닌텐도 DSi 기억합니까?
Super D I see like it's like a cartridge
내가 같이 볼 슈퍼 D는 카트리지처럼
yeah a tiny like I'm like when you say
예 , 당신이 말할 때처럼 작은 것 같아요.
cartridge it's like a thumbnail
thumbnail과 같은 카트리지
cartridge case job could they not
카트리지 케이스 일은 할 수 있지 않았다
exploit a cartridge could they not like
카트리지를 이용하면 좋지 않을 수있다.
infect a run of games for example and
예 를 들어 게임을 감염시키고
then because you turn on the switch and
스위치를 켜면
boom you're in I suppose but there's
붐 당신은 내가 가정에있어하지만 거기
always a boot sequence before you load
로드하기 전에 항상 부팅 순서
the game so just where do you put the
당신 이 게임을 어디에 놓을까요?
game in before you boot it isn't that
부팅하기 전에 게임을하지 않아도됩니다.
how you do it well yes but you still
당신은 아직도 네 잘 할 수 있지만 방법
have to boot into into the software in
에서 소프트웨어 로 부팅해야 합니다.
order to be able to read the game so you
순서는 그래서 게임을 읽을 수 있어야합니다
would go Pat this is my my guess from
이에서 내 내 생각이다 팻에게 갈 것
what the story is you boot into the
그 이야기는 당신 이
software first then access the game it'd
소프트웨어가 먼저 게임에 액세스하면
be no different than starting up your
시작 다르지 수 없습니다 당신의
Raspberry Pi and then being able to
라즈베리 파이와 그 다음에 할 수있는 것
access retropie just by having retropie
레트로 피를 만져서 레트로 피에 접근 해라.
on there doesn't change the boot
거기에 부팅을 변경하지 않습니다
sequence unless there's a way to change
시퀀스 를 변경 하지 않는 한 시퀀스
the coding somehow which I suppose is
어떻게 든 코딩 은
possible but again it if it's a if it's
그것의 경우 가능하지만, 다시 그것은 있다면
a line drive that you're sticking in
당신이 고집 하는 라인 드라이브
your switch you'd have to physically
당신 이 물리적으로해야 할 스위치
impact that drive now so I mean who
지금 운전에 미치는 영향은 그래서 나는 사람을 의미
knows it's possible I guess I mean it's
그것이 가능하다고 알고 나는 그것의 의미 같아요
still a new exploit but in the
여전히 새로운 익스플로잇이지만
interested in severs definitely
벌인 관심이 확실히
sideloading games custom games indie
사이드로드 게임 맞춤 게임 인디
games being able to release games that
게임을 출시 할 수있는 게임
you can play on a on a rooted switch
뿌리 박은 스위치로 재생할 수 있습니다 .
that yeah you can all of a sudden hey
예, 당신은 갑자기 어쩌면 그렇게 될 수 있습니다.
you know well I mean imagine people take
당신이 잘 알고 나는 사람들이 가지고 상상 의미
all those roms you've got from Sega
세가 에서 얻은 모든 롬들.
retropie on your switch now you've got
지금 당신이 가지고있는 스위치의 레트로 피
retropie on the go there you go it's
거기에 retropie 가서 당신은 그것의
crazy stuff here it's a fun console and
미친 물건은 여기 재미있는 콘솔이고
it can be even more fun soon do you run
그것은 곧 실행 할 더 많은 재미를 할 수 있습니다
Drupal you need to upgrade immediately
당신은 즉시 업그레이드해야 Drupal
as an in the wild exploit aims to take
사나운 공략 에서
over your server attackers are mass
서버상의 공격자는 대량입니다.
exploiting a recently fixed
최근에 수정 된 악용
vulnerability in the Drupal content
드루팔 (Drupal) 콘텐츠의 취약성
management system that allows them to
에 수 관리 시스템
take complete control of powerful
강력한 힘을 완전히 발휘하다
website servers
웹 사이트 서버
at least three different attack groups
적어도 세 가지 다른 공격 그룹
are exploiting a Drupal getting to the
드루팔 (Drupal) 을 이용 하여
name given to an extremely critical
매우 중요한에 주어진 이름
vulnerability that Drupal maintains
Drupal이 유지하는 취약성
maintainer is patched in late March
관리자가 3 월 말에 패치 됩니다.
Drupal getting to makes it easy for
드루팔에 점점 것은 쉽게
anyone on the internet to take complete
인터넷 에 있는 모든 사람 이 완료해야합니다.
control of vulnerable servers simply by
단순히 취약한 서버 제어
accessing a URL and injecting a publicly
URL에 액세스하고 공개적으로 삽입하기
available exploit code exploits allow
사용 가능한 악용 코드 악용 가능
attackers to run code of their choice
공격자 가 선택한 코드를 실행합니다.
without having having to have an account
계정을 가질 필요없이
of any type of of any pardon me of any
모든 종류의 사면
type on a vulnerable web site the mass
취약한 웹 사이트 에 유형을 입력 하십시오 .
exploitation of Drupal servers reminds
드루팔 (Drupal) 서버 이용은 상기시켜줍니다.
us of the epidemic of unpatched Windows
패치되지 않은 Windows 의 전염병
servers a decade ago which gave criminal
10 년 전에 범죄를 저지른 서버
hackers access to millions of pcs the
해커 수백만의 PC에 액세스
attackers would then use their widely
공격자는 폭넓게 사용할 것입니다.
distributed purchase to launch new
새로운 구매 를위한 분산 된 구매
instructions because web servers have
웹 서버는
significantly more computing power and
훨씬 더 많은 컴퓨팅 능력 과
Internet bandwidth than a desktop
데스크톱보다 인터넷 대역폭
computer the new rash of servers being
컴퓨터가 서버의 새로운 발진이되고있다.
compromised by this exploit poses a much
이 악용에 의해 손상 되면
greater threat to the Internet
인터넷에 대한 더 큰 위협
Drupal maintained errs have patched the
드루팔 (Drupal) 은 실수로
critical vulnerability in both the seven
7 명 모두에서 치명적인 취약점
point seven and eight version families
포인트 7 및 8 버전 제품군
as well as the six family which maintain
유지 하는 6 명의 가족 뿐만 아니라
errs stopped supporting in 2016
2016 년에 지원 중단됨
administrators who have yet to install
아직 설치하지 않은 관리자
the patch should assume their systems
패치는 그들의 시스템을 가정해야한다.
are compromised and take immediate
타협을 당하고 즉각 취하다.
action to disinfect them scary stuff it
무서운 것들을 소독 하는 행동
happens every week I feel Drupal and
매주마다 나는 Drupal과
insert you know anything else WordPress
당신은 다른 것을 알고 삽입 WordPress에
so you have to just update and like and
그래서 당신은 업데이트하고 좋아 해야합니다.
you have to run you know your security
당신 은 당신의 보안을 알아야합니다.
patches and everything you have to
패치 및 필요한 모든 것
install them and it has to happen all
를 설치하고 모든 일이있다
the time
시간
my question is why exactly would
내 질문은 왜 정확히
somebody not do that I feel like
누군가 내가 그런 기분이 들지 않는다.
wouldn't all of these news stories be
이 모든 뉴스 기사가
gone if people just updated when they
사람들이 방금 업데이트했을 때 사라졌습니다.
were
있었다
to update yes but that would require the
예 를 업데이트 할 수는 있지만
human race to not be lazy and really
게으르지 않고 정말로 인류가
that's about the only way to put it it
그건 그것을 넣는 유일한 방법입니다.
for people who are going to run a server
서버 를 돌릴 사람들을 위한
run a website you have to have to be
당신이해야 할 웹 사이트를 실행
security conscious so every day you
보안 의식이 있으므로 매일
should be looking to see is there
거기에 있는지 보고 있어야 한다.
something where my system is at risk
내 시스템이 위험한 곳
where my user data is at risk thinking
내 사용자 데이터가 위험 생각하고있는 곳
back to the government office who can't
정부 관청으로
keep up with the technology you think
생각하는 기술을 따라 잡으십시오.
about Drupal and content management
드루팔 (Drupal 및 콘텐츠 관리)
systems get put into place because their
시스템은 그들의
cost savings we don't have to develop
우리가 개발할 필요가없는 비용 절감
the backend we can create a content
백엔드는 콘텐츠를 만들 수 있습니다 .
management site our cost goes down now
관리 사이트는 우리의 비용은 지금 내려갑니다
if our cost goes down part of that
우리 비용이 그 부분의 일부가된다면
mentality is let's keep costs down so
정신력은 비용을 낮추 도록
maintenance falls by the wayside and
정비 는 길가에 떨어지고
nobody is keeping active maintenance
아무도 적극적인 유지 보수를하지 못한다.
going with these websites so you know
이 웹 사이트 와 함께
you see it all the time people buy these
당신은 항상 사람들이 구매 참조
cheap websites based on its content
그것의 내용에 근거를 둔 싼 웹 사이트
management website service because they
관리 웹 사이트 서비스 때문에
don't have to pay a lot of money upfront
선행 많은 돈을 지불 할 필요가 없습니다
but you do have to maintain it and if
그러나 당신은 그것을 유지해야 하고 만약에
you don't you're gonna be one of those
너는 그 중 하나가 될 수 없어.
exploited thanks Robbie and big thanks
착취 감사 로비와 큰 감사
to Roy W Nash and our community of yours
Roy Wash와 우리 공동체에
for submitting story sauce this week
이번 주에 이야기 소스 제출하기
thanks for watching the category-five TV
카테고리 -5 TV 를 시청 해 주셔서 감사합니다.
newsroom don't forget to Like and
뉴스 룸 이 좋아하는 것을 잊지 마라.
subscribe for all your tech news with a
기술 뉴스를 구독하려면
slight Linux bias and for more free
약간의 리눅스 바이어스 와 더 많은 무료
content be sure to check out our website
내용은 우리의 웹 사이트를 체크 아웃해야합니다
from the category-five TV newsroom I'm
난 범주 다섯 TV의 뉴스 룸에서
Sasha Rickman
사샤 릭맨
[Music]
[음악]
[Applause]
[박수 갈채]